this is for Ned and I apologize in
advance for your ears I'm not a singer a
I like it already walking down the
street I'm hoping to run into you and I
do but you've killed yourself this is
embarrassing when people describe you
they'll often just say dead but to me
you'll always be steinard and
Comm 911 what's your emergency a man
died and he's dead in the night I miss
you I call out your we need an ambulance
with a coffin not my voice if you
haded I'd still feel the same just
sounds like me it's not me my name is
Billy Brown my hair is blonde no no
honey blonde why do I keep describing my
hair so much I will never forget you
I don't know his name it's not really
happen it's not really you know what
makes me laugh Billy you're exactly like
Ned I'm not him I'm not him you have his
face his glasses his hair and his
job hey Billy you're NAD what are you
talking I'm not mad
I'm
Billy why are you laughing at me you're
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
steinard middle name I
believe thank you oh don't do that don't
clap don't uh for her why a man died and
she's just up there like oh boohoo song
I didn't cry you're both wearing denim
jackets to a memorial and you're all
clapping away clapping away it was
really just the coffee guy clapping oh
was it Mr big shot head of the
department BFFs you know what just fire
me no don't fire her well I'm not going
to fire I I I can't fire someone for
doing a bad popey imitation in a dead
man's office mediocre and how did you
become friends with my boss best friends
best friends she totally reminds me of
Ned what did you just say um I I am my
own person
okay and this is whack all right y'all
having a Whack Attack okay I need you to
have some
R okay well you for the d r I think for
the day I'm sorry I have a thing with
funerals it just always happens problem
is leaving I'm normal I can be normal no
one says I'm normal who's normal someone
get my Yamaha we too gangu for TV that's
why you don't see us but they still want
to be